export const generalQuestions = [
  {
    value: "question-1",
    question: "When is the start and end of the convention?",
    answer:
      "Start around noon on Friday, April 18th and end around noon on Monday, April 21st.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-2",
    question:
      "What if I can't attend from the first day or until the last day of the convention?",
    answer:
      "If you are unable to attend the convention from the first day or stay until the last day, that's absolutely fine. Our event is flexible, and we understand that attendees may have different schedules. Please make sure to inform the registration contact person in advance about your specific attendance dates and any schedule adjustments.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-3",
    question:
      "Do I still have to pay in full even if I am not there for the entire duration?",
    answer:
      "Unfortunately yes.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-4",
    question: "Is there any possibility to attend the convention online?",
    answer: "Unfortunately no.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-5",
    question: "In what language will the sessions be delivered?",
    answer: "Indonesian, with English or German translation via Headphones.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-6",
    question: "Are there separate sessions for kids and teenagers?",
    answer:
      "Yes, there will be 3 age-based separate sessions for kids and teenagers.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-7",
    question:
      "Are Good Friday and Easter services going to be held during the convention?",
    answer: "Yes.",
  },
];

export const registrationQuestions = [
  {
    value: "question-1",
    question: "What is included in the registration fee?",
    answer:
      "Seminars, meals (breakfast, lunch, dinner), accommodation and bed sheets.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-2",
    question: "When is the deadline to register for the early bird price?",
    answer:
      "Registration and payment must be completed by January 31st, 2025.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-3",
    question: "Are there early bird prices for children and teenagers as well?",
    answer: "No.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-4",
    question: "Is there any special price for students?",
    answer: "No.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-5",
    question:
      "I am very interested in joining the convention but I am financially limited, what should I do?",
    answer:
      "Contact us at <a href='mailto:erec.ireceurope@gmail.com' class='underline'>erec.ireceurope@gmail.com</a> or get in touch with one of the contact persons listed on the website, we will find a solution together so that you can still join the event.",
  }
];

export const accommodationQuestions = [
  {
    value: "question-1",
    question: "Where is Halle (Saale)?",
    answer:
      "Halle (Saale) is a vibrant city located in the Saxony-Anhalt region of Germany. Known for its rich history, the city boasts a stunning medieval old town, featuring architectural gems like the Market Church of St. Mary and the Red Tower. Halle is also renowned for its cultural significance, with ties to famous figures like George Frideric Handel and a thriving arts scene, making it a captivating destination for both history enthusiasts and art aficionados.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-2",
    question: "Does the accommodation provide any baby crib?",
    answer: "Yes.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-3",
    question: "Is the accommodation accessible for wheelchairs?",
    answer:
      "Yes to a certain degree. Please get in touch with our registration point of contact.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-4",
    question:
      "Are there meal options for vegetarians or vegans or other dietician requirements?",
    answer: "Yes. You can specify your dietary restrictions on the registration form.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-5",
    question:
      "I'm going to bring my own car. Can I park at or near the accommodation?",
    answer: "Yes. Parking slots are available at the venue.",
  },
  {
    value: "question-6",
    question:
      "What should I do if I have a special condition that needs to be considered for room allocation?",
    answer: "Please give the details on the registration form or get in touch with our registration point of contact.",
  },
];

export const transportationQuestions = [
  {
    value: "question-1",
    question:
      "How to get there?",
    answer:
      "We will continue to update you if there is a strike in the days leading up to March 29, 2024. However, we can also recommend taking the bus (Flixbus), Flixtrain, or renting car for your journey or arriving in Halle earlier.",
  },
];
